relix.com 2019-12-05

# Privacy Policy

_Last Modified May 25, 2018_

At Relix, we and our readers are connected by a love of finding and spreading the word about great music, which means that sharing is one of our highest values. But maintaining the privacy of the personal information you entrust to us is even more important. This Privacy Policy explains how we use and share personal information we collect through our Relix.com and Jambands.com websites, through the electronic version, or “e-mag” of Relix we make available both online and on mobile devices such as the iPad, and through offline means such as telephone and postal mail.

As you may be aware, a new European Union law, called the General Data Protection Regulation (or “GDPR”), gives certain rights to individuals in relation to their personal data. To reflect the increased transparency requirements of the GDPR, we will be making some changes to our Privacy Policy and rolling out new tools to give you additional transparency and control over the personal data we collect and use, including a Marketing Preferences page that will help you more easily understand and manage your privacy choices.

By using our sites, subscribing to Relix magazine, or using any of our other products or services, you are accepting the practices we describe here.

What information do we collect?

Relix collects personal information, which you provide voluntarily, and non-personal usage information, which we collect using cookies and other technologies as you browse our sites or use our products or services.

Personal Information

Registration Information  
If you want to receive our email newsletter, participate in any of our contests or promotions, fill out a questionnaire or survey or engage in certain other activities on our sites, you will need to provide us with certain personal information. The specific information will vary depending on the activity, and may include your name, email address, mailing address, birth date and gender. If you’re not interested in participating, that’s cool – you are still free to browse our sites – but if you want to interact more deeply with what Relix has to offer, you will need to sign up and provide us with the requested information.

Financial Information  
In order to pay for Relix subscriptions, whether in print, as an e-mag or through a mobile application, you will need to provide valid billing and credit card information (your credit card number and expiration date, billing address, etc.). This information will only be shared with third parties who perform credit card processing, subscription fulfillment or other tasks required to deliver the purchased product or service. In some cases, the third parties we have contracted to perform the service will collect this information from you directly.

Usage Information

We also collect information that does not identify you personally, but gives us data about your computer and how you use our websites. This information includes your IP address, your browser type, operating system, the date and time you access the site, and the website that referred you to our site.

Cookies and other Technologies

We collect and store information using “cookies.” A cookie is a small text file stored on your computer, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, the web server asks your browser for permission to store this file, or “drop the cookie” on your computer or mobile device, which we then use to recognize you when you visit our sites. Cookies link to information we store regarding pages you have viewed or features you have used.

Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent on the websites, and the websites you visited just before and just after coming to our sites. We may also use “web beacons,” which track your use of our websites in order to provide you with a more personalized experience the next time you visit.

You can configure your browser’s settings regarding cookies by selecting “Internet Options” (IE), “Options” (Firefox and Chrome) or “Preferences” (Safari) or in the “Tools” menu of your browser. If you want, you can prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, have your browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or disable cookies altogether. However, some aspects of our websites will not function properly if you do not accept cookies.

Advertising

Our Advertisers

Relix’s advertisers and advertising vendors display targeted advertisements. Although we do not provide any personal information to the advertiser or advertising vendor, by interacting with or clicking on an ad you acknowledge the possibility that the advertiser may assume you meet the targeting criteria used.

In addition to our cookies and tracking technologies, as described above, advertisers and advertising vendors that serve ads on our websites may use their own. Their use of the non-personal information they collect is governed by their own privacy policies, and their practices are not under our control.

Relix works with Google AdSense and MediaMind for the delivery of advertisements to our websites. The non-personally-identifiable information they collect about your visits to our websites may be used to provide advertisements about goods and services they believe (based upon your previous behavior) may be of interest to you.

Please be aware that advertisers have links on our sites that take you to other sites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Use of the information collected by these third party sites will be governed by their own privacy policies, and Relix does not assume any responsibility for their actions. If you have any questions about how a third party handles personal information, please contact them directly.

What do we use your information for?

In general, Relix may use information that we collect about you in the following ways:

• to process payment for subscription purchases;  
• to deliver the products and services you request;  
• to manage your account and provide you with customer service;  
• to analyze your use of, or interest in, our products, services or content (or products, services or content offered by others on our websites);  
• to communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that we think may be of interest to you;  
• to help us develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests;  
• to verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes;  
• to enforce our terms and conditions;  
• to protect against or identify fraudulent transactions; and  
• to generally manage our business.

Do we share any information with outside parties?

Relix shares corporate ownership with Brooklyn Bowl, The Capitol Theatre and the Lockn’ Festival. Accordingly, Relix may disclose your name, email address and zip code to its affiliated companies operating these venues to enable them to market concerts and other events they think you might be interested in. If at any point you do not want to continue receive email messages from Relix or any of its affiliates, please follow the unsubscribe instructions in the relevant email.

Relix may also disclose your personal information to companies we engage as contractors or agents to perform services for us, such as fulfilling print or electronic magazine subscriptions, maintaining software, providing email marketing or administering a sweepstakes or contest. We share information with these contractors only to the extent reasonably necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf, and pursuant to confidentiality obligations.

We may also share your personal information collected in connection with a service, contest, sweepstakes, promotion or questionnaire with the third party partners or sponsors, or otherwise in accordance with the rules of the event. You should carefully review the rules, if any, of these events, as they may contain additional important information about a sponsor’s or other third party’s use of your personal information.

We may also disclose your personal information if we are legally compelled to do so. In other words, when the law requires it or when we have reason to believe that a disclosure is necessary or appropriate to address potential or actual injury or interference with the rights, property or operations of Relix, our users or others. Finally, if we undergo a merger or acquisition, or sell or otherwise transfer substantially all the assets of Relix Media Group LLC or its affiliates, or relating to any web site that we own or operate or any product or service that we offer, your personal information may be transferred to our successor or assign.

We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for general business analysis purposes. This aggregated data does not contain any personal information.

Your options

At any time, you can manage your email preferences and other aspects of your profile, including opting out of receiving newsletters and promotional emails from Relix, by clicking on the link at the bottom of any email that says “Manage your email profile.” You may also opt out from such emails completely by clicking on the link at the bottom of any email that says “Leave this email list.”  It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request.

Even if you have unsubscribed from receiving promotional emails from us, we may send you other types of important email communications, such as customer service communications and announcements, purchase notifications and confirmations, administrative notices, and surveys. You cannot opt out of receiving such service communications.

How does Relix protect your information?

We use industry standard technology and services to protect and secure your information. We will never initiate any email communication with you that requests your private information. In general, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Please contact Relix customer support if you have any questions or concerns.

Modification of Privacy Policy by Relix

Relix reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice explaining the changes. You will be deemed to have accepted such change if you continue to use our website after the revised policy has been posted.

Read more: https://relix.com/about#ixzz4wl2xqGi3
